<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TOUR GUIDE OF PORTO</string>
    <string name="monumentos">Monumentos</string>
    <string name="gastronomia">Gastronomia</string>
    <string name="caves">Caves</string>
    <string name="restaurante">Restaurantes</string>
    <string name="cave1">Cave Ramos Pinto</string>
    <string name="detail_cave1">Founded in 1880 by Adriano Ramos Pinto the winery has become one of the most famous in Oporto. In the visit you will have access to the office of Adriano converted into a museum.</string>
    <string name="cave2">Cave Sandeman</string>
    <string name="detail_cave2">Famous in addition to its wines for its mysterious logo, Sandeman is one of the most international wine brands in Porto. On this visit the guide will accompany you dressed as the "Don Sandeman".</string>
    <string name="cave3">Cave Ferreira</string>
    <string name="detail_cave3">Without being as well known as the previous ones, Bodega Ferreira is one of the most special in Porto. It is built on an old convent and the visit is well worth it.</string>
    <string name="cave4">Cave Wiese and Krohn</string>
    <string name="detail_cave4">This winery is quite small compared to others, and is not that nice, but if you want to try a good Port wine not far from the river in a winery, this is your place!</string>
    <string name="cave5">Cave Offley</string>
    <string name="detail_cave5">Founded by an English businessman, the Offley winery is among the oldest in Oporto. It offers one of the cheapest guided tours, and you can even buy a pack to take a boat trip on the river Douro also at a great price.</string>
    <string name="monument_1">Catedral da Sé de Porto</string>
    <string name="detail_monument1">Built in the highest part of the city and presiding over Porto is the Cathedral, the most important religious building in the city and one of the must-see visits.</string>
    <string name="monument_2">Igreja e Torre dos Clérigos</string>
    <string name="detail_monument2">The Clérigos Tower is the highest tower in Portugal and one of the symbols of Porto. From the top of the tower you will have the best views of the city.</string>
    <string name="monument_3">Estação de São Bento</string>
    <string name="detail_monument3">Built at the beginning of the 9th century on the remains of the former convent of São Bento de Ave Maria, this train station is one of the most special visits of Porto.</string>
    <string name="monument_4">Livraria Lello e Irmão</string>
    <string name="detail_monument4">A place of inspiration for the author of the Harry Potter saga, Livraria Lello e Irmão is one of the most beautiful places in Porto. His bookshelves and his thousands of books are a dream scenario.</string>
    <string name="monument_5">Avenida dos Aliados</string>
    <string name="detail_monument5">This huge square represents the heart of Porto life, where you can enjoy the majestic modernist architecture of buildings such as the town hall. It is in the center of the city, the best place to choose hotel, or hostel!</string>
    <string name="monument_6">Ponte Luis I</string>
    <string name="detail_monument6">Built in 1888 by Théophile Seyrig, disciple of Gustave Eiffel, he represents together with the Riveira the magic of the city. Is in a totally genuine place of light, laughter, music, and color, could be the soul of Porto. Obviously a must visit and besides both day and night!</string>
    <string name="monument_7">Casa da Música</string>
    <string name="detail_monument7">Built for the project "Porto 2001, European Capital of Culture" and with an avant-garde architecture, Casa da Música is one of the symbols of the new Port.</string>
    <string name="monument_8">Igreja de São Francisco</string>
    <string name="detail_monument8">Com um interior excessivamente ostentoso e umas pequenas catacumbas, a Igreja de São Francisco é, junto com a Catedral e os Clérigos, um dos edifícios mais importantes da cidade. </string>
    <string name="monument_9">Jardins do Palácio de Cristal</string>
    <string name="detail_monument9">Located in the upper part of Porto, the Cristal Palace Gardens are a beautiful place to rest. Its lookouts offer great views of the city.</string>
    <string name="monument_10">Parque da ciudade</string>
    <string name="detail_monument10">With 83 hectares of green areas the "Parque da Cidade" is the largest park in Portugal. It is a rather special case, as part of its extension is made on the margins of the Atlantic Ocean. It is also full of life, it is rare to walk around and there is no event. Pruba, I am sure you are lucky!</string>
    <string name="restaurant_1">Café Santiago</string>
    <string name="detail_restaurant1">Café Santiago is a restaurant in Porto, which is already a case of national and international notoriety due to the famous Francesinhas. Its fame already goes beyond borders and every year we receive hundreds of tourists and Portuguese who come to taste this delicious delicacy.</string>
    <string name="restaurant_2">Café Majestic</string>
    <string name="detail_restaurant2">Majestic coffee is one of those appointments that is not missing in any guide about Porto. A special corner where you enter to contemplate the sumptuous decoration or sit on its terrace located in one of the most important shopping areas of the city.</string>
    <string name="restaurant_3">Casa do Pescador</string>
    <string name="detail_restaurant3">Although it is not in the most typical of the city and is a little out of the way, it is the site of porto that best relation has between service, quality, and price. Typical place of the land, of all life, humble simple, and with the best seafood and octopus rice, etc. If you are a sea person and want to eat well, do not hesitate, you will not regret it.</string>
    <string name="restaurant_4">Casa Guedes</string>
    <string name="detail_restaurant4">A very small restaurant specializing in one of the delights of Porto, the Pernil sandwiches. It makes up for how small the restaurant is with how big the terrace is. The situation is great, beautiful and with atmosphere, what more can you ask for?</string>
    <string name="restaurant_5">Venham mais 5</string>
    <string name="detail_restaurant5">The best Prego no pão in the whole city, and besides the pies they make are irresistible. It has an indoor terrace inside if it rains and is also very well placed to eat while tourists.</string>
    <string name="restaurant_6">Taberninha do Manel</string>
    <string name="detail_restaurant6">If you are already looking for something more restaurant to try dishes also typical, but more elaborate, the taberninha de Manel is the best to go a day of good time to enjoy its food of great quality and the unbeatable views of the ribeira of Porto and the bridge Luis I.</string>
    <string name="restaurat_7">Mal Cocinhado</string>
    <string name="detail_restaurant_7">To get into the old and classic Porto, this underground restaurant (but super well adapted) will undoubtedly fall in love with its romanticism, live Fado shows and its super affordable menus.</string>
    <string name="restaurant_8">Conga</string>
    <string name="detail_restaurant8">Next to Aliados Avenue, this place is perfect in case you get hungry and want to try something different and surprise yourself, the Bifanas. It is also very curious to see the cooks prepare this little gem of Portuguese gastronomy.</string>
    <string name="gastronomy_1">Francesinha</string>
    <string name="detail_gastronomy1">The francesinha is a sandwich, stuffed with meats (sausages, sausages, steak and ham, among others like roasted meat) covered with cheese that, in the end, is gratinado and takes the hot sauce on top. Sometimes because it also has star fish, shellfish (prawns) and can be served with chips.No doubt it is the most typical and most famous dish of Porto, and yes, it is a sandwich and also loaded with calories, but it is unforgivable to pass through Porto and not try it, because you will regret 100% sure.</string>
    <string name="gastronomy_2">Sandes de pernil</string>
    <string name="detail_gastronomy2">With this dish happens the same as with many, you have to know where to go, but if you can find the good ones, you will enjoy a pork sandwich roasted in their sauce, which you can accompany with cheese. One of my favorites. Do not even miss it!</string>
    <string name="gastronomy_3">Prego no pão</string>
    <string name="detail_gastronomy3">Nail bread with queso da serra, the first thing to say is that the quality of this dish varies enormously depending on where you take it, but if you know where to go, you can enjoy a loaf of bread with prime beef tenderloin and melted cheese from the earth. Seems little thing? I assure you it is not!</string>
    <string name="gastronomy_4">Bifana</string>
    <string name="detail_gastronomy4">The bifanas can be served on a plate or bread roll, although the latter is the most typical in Porto. The meat, previously marinated, is boiled in a tomato sauce, and it is common to see the pots with the sauce boiling in the Storefronts of the establishments that offer them. It is possible that it chop a little, but not too much, dare to try it!</string>
    <string name="gastronomy_5">Bacalhau à Brás</string>
    <string name="detail_gastronomy5">There are a thousand dishes cooked with cod, and any one of them is great, but without doubt the one that stands out is Bacalhau à Brás is a typical recipe of Portuguese cuisine that carries cod, as well as potatoes and egg. It is a very popular dish in almost all the Portuguese territory, and besides that its flavor is unique, the presentation of the dish returns us to surprise.</string>
    <string name="gastronomy_6">Alheira</string>
    <string name="detail_gastronomy6">Alheira is a sausage typical of Portuguese cuisine whose main ingredients are minced meat, both pork and poultry, bread, oil, garlic and paprika. There are several ways to prepare them, and certainly the taste and texture surprise in a delicious way.</string>
    <string name="gastronomy_7">Peixe</string>
    <string name="detail_gastronomy7">To talk about fresh fish and seafood, it is not easy to choose a restaurant to eat fish in the Greater Porto Area. They are many and many of them are very good. Two of the neighboring towns of Porto, Matosinhos and Vila Nova de Gaia are known for their fresh fish and seafood restaurants.</string>
    <string name="gastronomy_8">Pastéis de Nata</string>
    <string name="detail_gastronomy8">The Natas de Belém are one of the most characteristic specialties of Portuguese cuisine. Although they are really coming from Lisbon, they have taken so much fame that now they are prepared in any part of Portugal, reason why also you can enjoy them in Oporto. Generically they are called cream cakes. They are cream pancakes, about 8 centimeters in diameter.</string>
</resources>
